Guide to the Abraham Hayward correspondence files: 1063 items, 1790-1889
The New York Public Library. Carl H. Pforzheimer Collection of Shelley and His Circle.
- Peel, Emily Hay, Lady, d. 1924, Drayton Manor, Tamworth - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 14 March 1873; HWD 01.012; autograph letter signed
- Peel, Emily Hay, Lady, d. 1924 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 1 March 1860; HWD 01.013; autograph letter signed
- Peel, Emily Hay, Lady, d. 1924, Whitehall Gardens - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 25 December 1872; HWD 01.016; autograph letter signed
- Peel, Emily Hay, Lady, d. 1924, Drayton Manor, Tamworth - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 23 January 1878; HWD 01.017; autograph letter signed
- Peel, Emily Hay, Lady, d. 1924, Drayton Manor, Tamworth - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 12 May 1878; HWD 01.018; autograph letter signed
- Peel, Laurence, 1801-1888, 32 Sussex Square, Brighton - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 17 November 1874; HWD 04.017; autograph letter signed
- Peel, Robert, Sir, 1822-1895 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 21 October [no year]; HWD 06.061; autograph letter signed
- Peel, Robert, Sir, 1822-1895, Whitehall - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 2 April 1860; HWD 04.008; autograph letter signed
- Peel, Robert, Sir, 1822-1895, Whitehall - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 23 July 1861; HWD 01.065; autograph letter signed
- Peel, Robert, Sir, 1822-1895, Whitehall - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 23 April 1860; HWD 02.005; autograph letter signed
- Pell, Alfred, 89 Madison Avenue, New York - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 12 November 1861; HWD 06.094; autograph letter signed
- Phillpotts, Henry, 1778-1869, Bishopston - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 2 January 1860; HWD 01.008; autograph letter signed
- Pigot, David Richard, 1797-1873, Dublin, 52 Stephen's Green East - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 11 August 1853; HWD 08.003; autograph letter signed
- Planche, J. R. (James Robinson), 1796-1880, College of Arms - to Winchilsea, George James Finch-Hatton, Earl of, 1815-1887, w/m = 18[7?]1; HWD 05.030; autograph letter signed
- Planche, J. R. (James Robinson), 1796-1880, 20 Brompton Crescent - to Winchilsea, George James Finch-Hatton, Earl of, 1815-1887, 29 June 1841; HWD 05.031; autograph letter signed
- Platt, Thomas Joshua, Sir, 1788 or 90-1862 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 27 May 1846; HWD 06.042; autograph letter signed
- Pollington, Venetia - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, [18]78[?] (from notation in unknown hand); HWD 07.082; autograph letter signed
- Pollock, F. (Frederick), Sir, 1783-1870 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 11 May 1842; HWD 04.012; autograph letter signed
- Pollock, F. (Frederick), Sir, 1783-1870, Hatton Middlx - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 11 January 1856; HWD 08.082; autograph letter signed
- Pollock, F. (Frederick), Sir, 1783-1870 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 21 May 1842; HWD 06.019; autograph letter signed
- Ponsonby, Henry Frederick, Sir, 1825-1895, V. R. Lodge - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 8 July 1854; HWD 10.028; autograph letter signed
- Portland, William John Cavendish-Scott-Bentinck, Duke of, 1800-1879, 13, Grosvenor Place - to Winchilsea, Constance Henrietta Paget Finch, Countess of, d. 1878, HWD 05.035; autograph note signed
- Power, Marguerite A., 1815?-1867 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 4 October 1852; HWD 09.058; autograph letter signed
- Power, Marguerite A, 1815?-1867 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 9 December [no year]; HWD 04.019; autograph letter signed
- Power, Marguerite A., 1815?-1867 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 04.020; autograph letter signed
- Procter, Anne Benson, 1799-1888, 32 Weymouth St - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 9 February [no year]; MISC 3496; autograph letter signed
- Rawlinson, Henry Creswicke, Sir, 1810-1895 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 5 June 1860; HWD 04.085; autograph letter signed
  With envelope, with wax seal.
- Rawlinson, Henry Creswicke, Sir, 1810-1895 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 12 January 1860; HWD 04.084; autograph letter signed
  Blind stamp: HBM Persian Mission.
- Reay, Fanny Georgiana Jane Hasler, Baroness, 6 Great Stanhope Street, May Fair - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 02.054; autograph letter signed
- Reay, Fanny Georgiana Jane Hasler, Baroness, Laidlawsteil, Galashiels, N. B - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 21 October 1883; HWD 02.055; autograph letter signed
- Reeve, Henry, 1813-1895, Privy Council Office - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 03.061; autograph letter signed
- Reeve, Henry, 1813-1895, Privy Council Office - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 16 May [no year]; HWD 04.026; autograph letter signed
- Reid, Stuart J. (Stuart Johnson), 1848-1927, Wilmslow Cheshire - to [Miss Hayward], 1 October 1884; HWD 06.037; autograph letter signed
  to one of A. Hayward's sisters.
- Rennell, James, 1742-1830 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 04.096
  autograph notes on "the Decapolis".
  At the foot of the slip: "This is an autograph of Major Rennell's sent to me. C. S. Rennell". With "Charles Rennell, Esq." on the verso.
- Rogers, Samuel, 1763-1855, St. James's Place - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, "Saturday"; HWD 07.112; autograph letter signed
- Rogers, Samuel, 1763-1855 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 03.042; autograph letter signed
- Rogers, Samuel, 1763-1855 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 22 May 1841; HWD 07.115; autograph letter signed
- Rogers, Samuel, 1763-1855 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 28 July 1840; HWD 10.073; autograph letter signed
- Romilly, John Romilly, Baron, 1802-1874 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 4 January 1856; HWD 08.083; autograph letter signed
- Rose, George, Sir, 1782-1873, Hyde Park S - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 21 January 1840; HWD 01.009; autograph letter signed
- Rose, George, Sir, 1782-1873, Hyde Park Gardens - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 23 December 1854; HWD 04.013; autograph letter signed
- Rose, George, Sir, 1782-1873, Hyde Park Garden - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 25 December 1854; HWD 04.021; autograph letter signed
- Rose, George, Sir, 1782-1873.:, Hyde Park Gardens - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 23 June 1845; HWD 02.080; autograph letter signed
- Rothschild, Anthony Nathan de, Sir, 1810-1876, 148 Picadilly - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, "Sunday"; HWD 07.098; autograph letter signed
- Rothschild, Anthony Nathan de, Sir, 1810-1876, 148 Picadilly - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, "Thursday"; HWD 06.091; autograph letter signed
- Rothschild, Anthony Nathan de, Sir, 1810-1876, Gunnersbury, Acton - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 22 January 1873; HWD 04.022; autograph letter signed
- Rothschild, Louisa Montefiore Rothschild, Baroness de, d. 1910, 148 Piccadilly - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 19 June 1872; MISC 3517 d; autograph letter signed
- Rothschild, Louisa Montefiore Rothschild, Baroness de, d. 1910, 148 Piccadilly - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 20 September 1870; MISC 3517 c; autograph letter signed
- Rothschild, Louisa Montefiore Rothschild, Baroness de, d. 1910, 148 Piccadilly - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, MISC 3517 a; autograph letter signed
- Rothschild, Louisa Montefiore Rothschild, Baroness de, d. 1910, Kingston House - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, "Wednesday morning"; MISC 3517 b; autograph letter signed
- Rous, Henry John, 1795-1877, Newmarket - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 13 November 1862; HWD 09.092; autograph letter signed
- Russell, Arthur, 1825-1892, Abbey Woburn - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 19 January 1875; HWD 10.047; autograph letter signed
- Russell, Arthur, 1825-1892, Rome - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 31 December 1864; HWD 01.093; autograph letter signed
- Russell, Laura, Lady, d. 1910, 2 Audley Square. W - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 20 January 1878; HWD 09.083; autograph letter signed
- Rutland, John James Robert Manners, Duke of, 1818-1906, Belvoir Castle - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 4 March 1858; HWD 01.015; autograph letter signed
- Rutland, John James Robert Manners, Duke of, 1818-1906, 14 Cavendish Square - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 10 February 1852; HWD 01.021; autograph letter signed
- Rutland, John James Robert Manners, Duke of, 1818-1906, St. Katherine's Lodge, Regents Park - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 19 March 1859; HWD 01.014; autograph letter signed
- Sackville, Lionel Sackville Sackville-West, Baron, 1827-1908, Bordeaux - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 16 November 1865; HWD 04.104; autograph letter signed
- Salisbury, Georgina Charlotte Alderson Gascoyne-Cecil, Marchioness of, 1827-1899, Hatfield House - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, MISC 3514; autograph letter signed
- Sandhurst, William Rose Mansfield, Baron, 1819-1876, 18 Grosvenor Gardens - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 8 July 1871; HWD 07.030; autograph letter signed
- Sandwith, Humphry, 1822-1881, Llanrhaeadr Hall, Denbigh - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 27 November 1866; HWD 06.022; autograph letter signed
- Savage, M. W. (Marmion Wilard), 1803-1872, 13 Kensington Gate W - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, "Saturday Morning"; HWD 06.076; autograph letter signed
- Selborne, Maud Gascoyne-Cecil Palmer, countess of, 1858-1950, 20, Arlington St. S. W - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 17 May 1877; HWD 07.004; autograph letter signed
- Shaftesbury, Anthony Ashley Cooper, Earl of, 1801-1885 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 22 September 1869; HWD 10.091; autograph letter signed
- Shelley, Mary Wollstonecraft, 1797-1851, Putney - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 28 December 1839; MWS 0384; autograph letter signed
- Sherbrooke, Robert Lowe, Viscount, 1811-1892, 2 Paper Buildings, Inner Temple - to [?], 5 December 1851; HWD 08.027; autograph letter signed
  perhaps to Hayward.
- Sherbrooke, Robert Lowe, Viscount, 1811-1892, 11 Downing Street, Whitehall - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 21 October 1872; HWD 03.024; autograph letter signed
- Sherbrooke, Robert Lowe, Viscount, 1811-1892, 11 Downing Street, Whitehall - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 23 November 1871; HWD 03.013; autograph letter signed
- Sherbrooke, Robert Lowe, Viscount, 1811-1892, 34 Lowndes Square - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 20 January 1861; HWD 03.014; autograph letter signed
- Sherbrooke, Robert Lowe, Viscount, 1811-1892, 34 Lowndes Square - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 15 April 1856; HWD 03.017; autograph letter signed
- Sherbrooke, Robert Lowe, Viscount, 1811-1892, 34 Lowndes Square - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 16 March 1864; HWD 03.016; autograph letter signed
- Sherbrooke, Robert Lowe, Viscount, 1811-1892, 11 Downing Street, Whitehall - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 03.015; autograph letter signed
- Sinclair, Tollemache, Sir, 1825-1912, 89 Eaton Place S. W - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 7 July 1879; HWD 10.041; autograph letter signed
- Slidell, John, 1793-1871, Paris - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 8 November 1862; HWD 06.015; autograph letter signed
- Slidell, John, 1793-1871, Paris - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 16 November 1862; HWD 06.010; autograph letter signed
- Slidell, John, 1793-1871, Paris - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 13 June 1862; HWD 06.011; autograph letter signed
- Slidell, John, 1793-1871, Paris - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 8 August 1862; HWD 06.012; autograph letter signed
- Slidell, John, 1793-1871, Paris - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 30 October 1862; HWD 06.013; autograph letter signed
- Slidell, John, 1793-1871, Paris - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 12 November 1862; HWD 06.014; autograph letter signed
- Slidell, Marie Mathilde Deslonde, 37 Chaqmps Elysees - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 7 May 1862; HWD 09.027; autograph letter signed
- Smith, Rosalind, b. 1821, 16 Cumberland St - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 07.088; autograph letter signed
  daughter of Horace Smith.
- St. Albans, William Amelius Aubrey de Vere Beauclerk, Duke of, 1840-1898, Osborne Cottage, Isle of Wight - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 18 December 1869; MISC 3498; autograph letter signed
- St. Germans, Edward Granville Eliot, Earl of, 1798-1877 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 01.045; autograph letter signed fragment
- St. Germans, Edward Granville Eliot, Earl of, 1798-1877 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 2 February 1855; HWD 01.044; autograph letter signed
- St. Germans, Edward Granville Eliot, Earl of, 1798-1877 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 14 February 1855; HWD 01.042; autograph letter signed
- St. Germans, Edward Granville Eliot, Earl of, 1798-1877 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 5 January 1855; HWD 01.043; autograph letter signed
- St. Germans, Edward Granville Eliot, Earl of, 1798-1877, Port Eliot - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 23 June 1855; HWD 01.047; autograph letter signed
- St. Germans, Edward Granville Eliot, Earl of, 1798-1877 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 26 February 1855; HWD 03.018; autograph letter signed
- St. Germans, Edward Granville Eliot, Earl of, 1798-1877 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 27 February 1855; HWD 01.046; autograph letter signed
- St. Germans, Edward Granville Eliot, Earl of, 1798-1877 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 3 March 1855; HWD 08.040; autograph letter signed
- St. Germans, Edward Granville Eliot, Earl of, 1798-1877, Dover St - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 26 February 1859; HWD 08.041; autograph letter signed
- St. Germans, Edward Granville Eliot, Earl of, 1798-1877, Dover St - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, "Wednesday"; HWD 03.065; autograph letter signed
- St. Germans, Edward Granville Eliot, Earl of, 1798-1877, Port Eliot - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 4 January 1868; MISC 3504; autograph letter signed
- St. Germans, Edward Granville Eliot, Earl of, 1798-1877 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 24 July 1854; HWD 08.043; autograph letter signed
- St. Germans, Edward Granville Eliot, Earl of, 1798-1877 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 16 February 1855; HWD 01.003; autograph letter signed
- St. Germans, Edward Granville Eliot, Earl of, 1798-1877 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 4 February 1855; HWD 01.002; autograph letter signed
- Stanhope, Emily Harriet Kerrison Stanhope, Countess, d. 1873 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 28 September 1869; HWD 09.097; autograph letter signed
- Stanhope, Emily Harriet Kerrison Stanhope, Countess, d. 1873 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 18 September 1869; HWD 09.098; autograph letter signed
- Stanhope, Philip Henry Stanhope, Earl, 1781-1855, Hawkins Hotel - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, "Tuesday morning"; HWD 06.097; autograph letter signed
- Stanhope, Philip Henry Stanhope, Earl, 1805-1875 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 1 October 1857; HWD 06.008; autograph letter signed
- Stanhope, Philip Henry Stanhope, Earl, 1805-1875, Chevening - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 6 November 1864; HWD 06.059; autograph letter signed
- Stanhope, Philip Henry Stanhope, Earl, 1805-1875, Chevening - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 11 January 1868; HWD 06.060; autograph letter signed
- Stanhope, Philip Henry Stanhope, Earl, 1805-1875, Chevening - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 4 August 1866; HWD 06.054; autograph letter signed
- Stanhope, Philip Henry Stanhope, Earl, 1805-1875, Chevening - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 3 October 1869; HWD 06.058; autograph letter signed
- Stanhope, Philip Henry Stanhope, Earl, 1805-1875, Grosvenor Place - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 6 July 1871; HWD 09.102; autograph letter signed
- Stanhope, Philip Henry Stanhope, Earl, 1805-1875, Chevening - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 27 December 1867; HWD 06.057; autograph letter signed
- Stanhope, Philip Henry Stanhope, Earl, 1805-1875, Chevening - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 11 November 1866; HWD 06.055; autograph letter signed
- Stanhope, Philip Henry Stanhope, Earl, 1805-1875, Athenaeum, Pall Mall - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 9 August [no year]; HWD 09.096; autograph letter signed
- Stanhope, Philip Henry Stanhope, Earl, 1805-1875, Chevening - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 3 February 1863; HWD 06.056; autograph letter signed
- Stanhope, Philip Henry Stanhope, Earl, 1805-1875, Hotel Vendome, Paris - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 24 October 1867; HWD 02.008; autograph letter signed
- Stanhope, Philip Henry Stanhope, Earl, 1805-1875 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 17 May [no year]; HWD 09.099; autograph letter signed
- Stanhope, Philip Henry Stanhope, Earl, 1805-1875, Chevening - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 22 January 1861; HWD 09.100; autograph letter signed
- Stanhope, Philip Henry Stanhope, Earl, 1805-1875, Oakley Park, Scole, Norfolk - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 13 November 1874; HWD 09.101; autograph letter signed
- Stanley of Alderley, Henrietta Maria Dillon-Lee Stanley, Baroness, 1807-1895, 40 Dover St - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 22 May 1883; MISC 3522; printed invitation with manuscript writing
- Stanley, Dorothy, Lady, d. 1926, 2 Richmond Terrace - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, Monday 3rd.; HWD 09.088; autograph letter signed
- Stephen, George, Sir, 1794-1879, 17 Kings Arms Yard, Coleman Street - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 1 November 1839; HWD 09.016; autograph letter signed
- Stewart-Mackenzie, Hannah Charlotte Hope-Vere, d. 1868, Braham Castle - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 11 November 1862; HWD 06.033; autograph letter signed
- Stirling Maxwell, William, Sir, 1818-1878, Keir near Dunblane N. B - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 29 November 1863; HWD 09.024; autograph letter signed
- Stirling Maxwell, William, Sir, 1818-1878, Keir, Dunblane, N. B - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 7 January 1875; HWD 05.014; autograph letter signed
- Stirling Maxwell, William, Sir, 1818-1878, Hotel Meurice, Rue de Rivoli (stationery) - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 2 July 1848; HWD 09.023; autograph letter signed
- Stirling Maxwell, William, Sir, 1818-1878, Keir, Dunblane - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 25 March 1857; HWD 05.020; autograph letter signed
- Stirling Maxwell, William, Sir, 1818-1878, Athenaeum Club, Pall Mall S. W - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 14 July 1873; HWD 09.025; autograph letter signed
- Stirling Maxwell, William, Sir, 1818-1878 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 11 December 1854; HWD 05.018; autograph letter signed
- Stirling Maxwell, William, Sir, 1818-1878, Keir, near Dunblane, N. B - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 27 January 1864; HWD 05.010; autograph letter signed
- Stirling Maxwell, William, Sir, 1818-1878, Keir, near Dunblane, N. B - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 6 August 1871; HWD 05.008; autograph letter signed
- Stirling Maxwell, William, Sir, 1818-1878, Western Club Glasgow - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 19 October 1864; HWD 05.011; autograph letter signed
- Stirling Maxwell, William, Sir, 1818-1878, Keir, near Dunblane, N. B - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 29 January 1864; HWD 05.012; autograph letter signed
- Stirling Maxwell, William, Sir, 1818-1878, Keir, near Dunblane, N. B - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 8 September 1865; HWD 05.013; autograph letter signed
- Stirling Maxwell, William, Sir, 1818-1878, Keir, Dunblane, N. B - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 26 November 1874; HWD 05.015; autograph letter signed
- Stirling Maxwell, William, Sir, 1818-1878, Edinburgh - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 26 January 1864; HWD 05.009; autograph letter signed
- Stirling Maxwell, William, Sir, 1818-1878, Keir, near Dunblane, N. B - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 21 November 1865; HWD 05.017; autograph letter signed
- Stirling Maxwell, William, Sir, 1818-1878, Keir, Dunblane - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 27 February 1872; HWD 05.007; autograph letter signed
- Stirling Maxwell, William, Sir, 1818-1878 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 05.019; autograph letter signed (fragment)
- Stirling Maxwell, William, Sir, 1818-1878, Keir, Dunblane - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 10 April 1857; HWD 05.054; autograph letter signed
- Stirling Maxwell, William, Sir, 1818-1878, Keir, near Dunblane - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 29 September 1867; MISC 3506; autograph letter signed
- Stirling Maxwell, William, Sir, 1818-1878, Keir, Dunblane - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 28 January 1868; HWD 05.022; autograph letter signed
- Stirling Maxwell, William, Sir, 1818-1878, Edinburgh - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 27 March 1861; HWD 05.021; autograph letter signed
- Stirling Maxwell, William, Sir, 1818-1878, Keir, near Dunblane, N. B - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 2 November 1865; HWD 05.016; autograph letter signed
- Storks, Henry Knight, Sir, 1811-1874, Palace Corfi - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 31 August 1862; HWD 09.057; autograph letter signed
- Storks, Henry Knight, Sir, 1811-1874 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 15 January 1863; HWD 01.095; autograph letter signed
- Storks, Henry Knight, Sir, 1811-1874, Palace Corfu - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 7 October 1862; HWD 10.008; autograph letter signed
- Storks, Henry Knight, Sir, 1811-1874, Palace Corfu - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 22 February 1859; HWD 06.018; autograph letter signed
- Storks, Henry Knight, Sir, 1811-1874, Palace Corfu - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 3 November 1859; HWD 06.020; autograph letter signed
- Strangford, Emily Anne Beaufort Smythe, Viscountess, d. 1887 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 7 June 1872; HWD 03.057; autograph letter signed
- Strangford, Emily Anne Beaufort Smythe, Viscountess, d. 1887, 10 Chapel Street, Park Lane - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 3 June [no year]; HWD 03.060; autograph letter signed
- Strangford, Emily Anne Beaufort Smythe, Viscountess, d. 1887, 10 Chapel Street, Park Lane - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 26 January 1875; HWD 03.059; autograph letter signed
- Strangford, Emily Anne Beaufort Smythe, Viscountess, d. 1887, 10 Chapel Street, Park Lane - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 1875; HWD 03.058; autograph letter signed
- Strangford, Emily Anne Beaufort Smythe, Viscountess, d. 1887, 10 Chapel Street, Park Lane - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 5 January 1874; HWD 03.056; autograph letter signed
- Strangford, George Augustus Frederick Percy Sydney Smythe, Viscount, 1818-1857 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 21 December 1848; HWD 05.092; autograph letter signed
- Strzelecki, Paul Edmund de, 1797-1873, Wilton House, Salisbury - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 14 June 1857; HWD 04.025; autograph letter signed
- Swinton, J. R. (James Rannie), 1816-1888, 33 Warwick House Pemlico - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 27 December [no year]; HWD 03.003; autograph letter signed
- Tait, Archibald Campbell, 1811-1882 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 18 November 1872; HWD 06.021; autograph letter signed
- Thackeray, William Makepeace, 1811-1863 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 29 December 1847; MISC 3497; autograph letter signed
- Tomline, George, 1813-1889, 1 Carlton House Terrace S. W - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 1868; HWD 03.071; autograph letter signed
- Tomline, George, 1813-1889 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 7 February 1856; HWD 09.006; autograph letter signed
- Tomline, George, 1813-1889, Ipswich - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 30 January 1857; HWD 09.065; autograph letter signed
- Torrington, George Byng, Viscount, 1812-1884, 4, Warwick Square S. W - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 10.049; autograph letter signed